mysmsmantra.com 2015-12-29

# Privacy Policy | My Sms Mantra

**Privacy Policy** ****MySMSmantra provides services to people who join the website either as non-paying members or paid users. As part of the registration process, you will be asked to provide certain personal information. Our policy is to protect the privacy of the members.

We may send users periodic emails containing information about the website, administrative notices about a user’s account, updates on new service features, usage tips relating to the services and user satisfaction questions.   
We may access user information for one of the following administrative purposes:

  1. To examine system accounting logs and other company records to resolve email and other system errors or problems.
  2. For billing purposes.

We at MySMSmantra provide you access to your profile information for the purpose of reviewing and/or updating information. In order to make any changes to your profile, you can go to the home page of the website, log into the account and click on the Profile to update your directory information. 

We at MySMSmantra protect user information, by utilizing all the appropriate technologies to prevent unauthorized access to the information you have provided our site. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure that the information provided is used appropriately. We have formulated appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to protect the information that we collect online. 

Since technologies keep changing, we reserve the right to change, modify, add or remove portions of our Privacy Policy or Conditions of Use at any time without any prior notice. Hence, you are required to review the Privacy Policy periodically. YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR REGULARLY REVIEWING THE MySMSmantra WEBSITE TO NOTICE THE MODIFICATIONS THAT ARE MADE. YOU SHALL BE CONSIDERED TO HAVE ACCEPTED SUCH MODIFICATIONS BY CONTINUING TO USE THE SERVICES AFTER SUCH MODIFICATIONS HAVE BEEN POSTED OR AFTER INFORMATION REGARDING SUCH MODIFICATIONS HAS BEEN SENT TO YOU. If at any time you are uncomfortable with the change, amendment or modification to the Privacy Policy or Conditions of Use and wish to cancel your membership, please notify us.
